Server Guardian Warboard — built with Codex
and GPT-5.6 for OpenAI Build Week.
Raw security logs are hard to scan, and risky to share.
Server Guardian Warboard is a read-only viewer that turns
honeypot-style events from a live decoy server
into an explainable game dashboard.
This is the public judging surface.
No account, and no write actions.
Privacy filtering happens in the backend,
before data ever reaches the browser.
Source addresses become stable bot aliases.
Login names are masked. The protected host is generalized.
Suspicious URLs and commands are defanged for safe display.
What you see here is everything the public can see.
The interface is fully bilingual.
One click switches every panel, nameplate, and dialogue line
between English and Korean — including the canvas battle scenes.
The choice is remembered locally in the browser.
Each view mode presents the same filtered event stream
for a different scanning workflow.
The RPG village visualizes activity as a living scene.
The map view shows aggregate origins.
And the NORAD view gives a classic operations-room overview.
All read-only, all privacy-filtered.
Deterministic demo scenes let judges evaluate
the experience even when live traffic is low.
?demo=skirmish replays a complete battle.
High-risk payload events can even trigger first-person dungeon
sequences — three weapons, three distinct choreographies.
For Build Week, Codex and GPT-5.6 added the bilingual interface,
the privacy boundary, deterministic demos, and QA gates.
Product, privacy, and design decisions stayed human.
The repository documents prior work vs. Build Week work.
A safer way to understand hostile automation,
without exposing the system it protects.